I like that flag.
How much?
What do you think of my pin?
That's nice.
Got it from a terrorist.
What type of explosive?
I just want to take out
the competition.
And the lucky recipient?
Jeremiah...
Dunmire.
That was difficult.
not tearing that guy's head off.
What you're getting is
a whole lot of justice
for a whole lot of people.
Where the contraband at?
Hey. Spence. I need to know. can
you really sell this shit fast?
I can sell this shit
in ten minutes.
Oh... three. crap three.
You owe the house
a hundred large.
I am the house.
I've got your back
if you've got mine.
Don't ever play me
like this again.
Either of you.
You restored Manfredi's license.
Dwight Manfredi has a code
that you lack.
You motherf...
Help!
- And just like that...
- Congratulations.
Open sesame.
"From humble beginnings
come great things."
Yeah.
Good to be back in business.
If that Dunmire
show up here again.
he'd better bring
the National Guard.
You got that right.
Get me the hell out of here.
Yes. sir.
You didn't invite
anybody over. did you?
No. sir.
You see this guy before?
No.
I have this.
Who the hell are you?
Mr. Dunmire.
I do apologize for the visit.
Last chance.
Why the hell are you here?
I was sent to kill you.
And who. pray tell.
sent you to do that?
I believe you know.
In my world.
trustworthiness is everything.
and he is not trustworthy.
And you were gonna kill me.
even though our paths
had never crossed.
That's about as immoral
as it gets. isn't it?
Morality is not a factor
in my profession.
but survival is.
Manfredi came to me.
hired me to perform a service.
but so clearly loathed me.
I suspect he has
ulterior motives.
and that's why I'm here.
I'm gonna kill him.
that's for certain.
But to destroy other people
in his life...
that would be my gift to you.
Son. you can leave us now.
You showed up at the right time.
Right.
Put Holloway
at table two. not four.
He's a kingmaker. does not sit
behind the oil lobby.
Faith. family and freedom.
No. no. no.
- The financial doc...
- And freedom...
has got to be in the packet.
otherwise we're screwed.
Just check every envelope.
I don't care
if it takes ten minutes
or ten years. Bye.
No flowers. The podium
cannot look like a funeral.
Just something brighter.
We're selling hope. Thank you.
Talk to me.
Confirmations
from DuVernay. Witherspoon.
and Harrison families.
Um. and we're still waiting
on the Pentecostal Coalition
rep to respond.
If the bishop shows. we're fine.
If he doesn't. light a candle
because we're dead.
And tell Cal
to stop rewriting his speech.
We've already tested it.
I told him.
I'll tell him.
Cal. the speech is so strong.
- and you already know it.
- Thank you.
Don't overthink it.
Trust me.
Yeah. You're right.
Hello?
Hey. things good over there?
Yeah. final push.
Checking every detail.
And I can't believe
I'm saying this.
but if all goes well tonight.
I think we'll have
a future governor on our hands.
I'm banking on it.
Somehow I don't think
you're gonna need Cal Thresher
in your back pocket.
It can't hurt. Margaret.
Politicians come in handy.
especially when you own 'em.
Miss me a little?
A little.
Miss you.
Oh. shit. No wonder
I never got married.
Keller donated that.
That's gonna be huge.
I'm not sure
the poster's big enough.
Oh. Cal. It's just
not big enough for you.
"Thresher for governor."
Presidency's next.
Looks good.
I think that'll hold.
No more smashburgers.
Answer me.
Are you going
to the Thresher thing tonight?
I wasn't invited.
- Oh. like that ever stopped you?
- Well...
We'll finish this later.
This room gives me the creeps.
Hello.
I'm ready to make the exchange.
There's a gas station near...
How about if I pick
the time and place?
Is that okay?
Such little faith.
I'll send you the address.
Mitch.
Yeah?
Get Bigfoot.
We're gonna need backup.
Music to my ears.
Please tell me something good.
He called.
I'm sending him the address.
No. no. No. fuck that.
I set the meeting.
- That's not happening.
- Listen to me.
I got to post up.
I got to put together a team.
This has to be flawless.
It will be.
One night. one party.
Fast turnaround. zero overhead.
Easy money.
I'll handle the invites.
Let's do it.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Bodhi. my soul brother.
So. look. I got
a little question. right?
Not even a question.
I need the keys.
It's one night.
Controlled. clean.
Big money.
Right to business. huh?
No "Long time. no see.
How are you?
How have you been?"
"Good. Tyson. thanks for asking.
Uh. actually. it's been
a little slow around here.
I've missed you."
Anyway. so-so. basically.
so me and Spencer.
we come up
on a big Molly connect.
And we gonna need a venue. man.
We need a venue.
Just X and some alcohol.
She gonna run point.
And that's why
you need my place?
We about to do this
in Bred-2-Buck?
Hell no.
Come on. Bodhi.
It-It's just like
the nitrous. man.
You remember how much you was
earning that night. right?
Yeah. I remember
the bruises. too.
What about Dwight?
He can't know about this.
He said he want me to earn.
so this is gonna be it.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure
he didn't mean this.
Come on. Bodhi. man.
H-How else am I supposed to earn
big. fast money? How?
You don't even
got to do nothing. Bodhi.
Dwight ain't gonna find out
about this.
And let's just say he does.
If he does.
then. shit. fuck it. it's on me.
Your name is not in it.
Blacking them windows.
Nobody got to know.
How did he rope you into this?
Actually...
it was my idea.
Well. fuck.
I take 25% of the door
and even split of the product.
I need the keys.
Great day for a bust. ain't it?
Let's do this.
You got the money?
- In the back.
- Okay.
Wait. Musso.
I know what you did.
What-What are you talking about?
You're a Fed. right?
Deductive reasoning.
hypotheticals. syllogism.
What?
No? Maybe you should read more.
You'll figure it out.
The thing is.
after you looked
at every logical possibility.
whatever remains.
no matter how illogical...
it might be it.
So I know you took Bevilaqua
and then you made it look
like I did it. No. please.
don't talk. We know the truth.
Save your fucking breath.
But here's what
I'd like you to do.
since we're such good friends.
Release Bevilaqua
and get me out of this bullshit
that you dragged me into.
Yes. He's in.
He's in because I wanted him in.
'cause he's a gangster
with no purpose
and he was gonna fuck up
your purpose. Yeah?
He stays in
until I say otherwise.
It's getting dark. Let's go.
You go in. make the exchange.
When we know you're clear.
we'll move.
- take him down.
- And then what?
Then justice is served.
End of story.
Yeah. You charge him. you
arraign him. you prosecute him.
and maybe even convict him
if he doesn't get off
on some fucking technicality.
How many years before
you put the needle in his arm?
How many years
of fucking appeals does he get
while those people
lie rotting in the ground?
That's justice?
It's what my partner
would have wanted.
Deacon's a legit target.
He's just old business.
not very high
on the Bureau's priority list.
Then why is he high on yours?
He killed my partner.
One of his bombs
outside of Sapulpa.
Twenty civilians died.
My partner tried to save
as many as he could.
- He didn't make it.
- Come on. John.
You sent me those fucking
pictures for a reason.
Women and children.
The sick fuck.
You want justice?
- Leave him to me.
- Yeah. well.
due process. that's what ensures
a better tomorrow.
Well. that didn't happen
for your partner.
and it didn't happen
for those people.
By the book. okay?
Throw that book
in the fucking fire. would you?
You picked a hell of a location.
Your guy's inside.
Arrived 15 minutes ago.
He's waiting.
Okay.
Backup's a quarter mile out.
Make the exchange.
and then we'll move in
and take this fucker down.
I want you to wear a wire
- for insurance.
- Rats wear wires.
You want proof? I'll come out
with a bomb. there's your proof.
This case needs to be airtight.
Wear the fucking thing.
What is this.
a fucking breath mint?
It's state-of-the-art.
Clean sound.
Just put it under your collar.
for fuck's sake.
When this is over. we're done.
If this deal holds.
then we're done.
Don't fuck it up.
You couldn't get a shittier van?
Here it is.
$150.000.
Clean bills.
What the fuck is this?
There was a disconnect.
Mr. Manfredi.
You asked me to perform
a service for you.
but it was obvious
you loathed me.
There was something
personal about it.
I...
Shut the fuck up.
Gun down.
On the table. Slow.
One move. you're gone.
- Get him up.
- Done.
Check him for tracking devices.
Didn't expect to be on the
wrong end of the double cross.
What is this static?
That's all I hear.
Not coming through.
Give it a second.
Get in.
You're good.
He ain't going nowhere.
All right. go.
Are you?
- Thank you.
Evening.
Ken. how are you?
Thanks for doing this.
Thank you so much. Hope
you're having a great night.
Thank you very. very much.
- Hi. how are you?
- Hi.
Good to see you.
Thank you for being here.
- So great to see you.
- Margaret. after you.
- Hi.
- Hello. ladies. how are you?
Nice to see you. Thank you
so much for being here tonight.
Thank you very. very much.
Well. Margaret. we sure do make
the political couple.
Well. we're both political.
but we're not a couple.
Oh. I beg to differ.
That is not the impression
that you and I are giving off.
Ah.
Mr. and Mrs. Sackrider.
so great to see you both.
Thanks for coming out tonight.
Anna.
Wouldn't have missed it. Cal.
Oh. I like the confidence.
You look lovely.
Good luck to you both tonight.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Enjoy the night.
You know. uh... I was thinking.
I'd like to bring you
into my administration.
Oh. really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm. In what role?
Oh. you decide.
That's very flattering. Cal.
Oh. this has nothing to do
with flattery.
This is survival.
so why don't we stop pretending?
What does Dwight want from me?
Maybe nothing.
Oh. you know better.
- That's between you and Dwight.
- Oh. no. no.
That's between the three of us.
and you sure as shit know that.
See. I didn't sign up for this.
I was supposed to be the bridge.
not the fire starter.
but maybe that's how things
are won nowadays...
fear. leverage.
conversations and deals
behind the curtains. But you.
you made the choice.
so that makes you part of it.
And like it or not.
you are now the Mafia moll.
I beg your pardon?
Oh. you don't have to beg
anything from me. sweetheart.
Ever.
Just make sure you're ready
when the time comes
because... win. lose or draw...
if this thing goes sideways.
it's not just my ass
they're after.
It's Dwight's and it's yours.
And although Dwight Manfredi
might be bulletproof.
I assure you. Margaret.
we are not.
Now smile.
Dr. Johnson.
Thank you so much for coming.
You remember Margaret?
- I do.
- Dr. Johnson.
- welcome.
- Thank you. Margaret.
Come on in.
What the fuck?
Make the exchange.
Why is it taking so long?
Fuck it. let's go.
Motherfucker.
Manfredi!
What do you want to let me go?
Nothing.
You're not going anywhere.
You must want something.
I want everything you know.
Every fucking client
you ever worked with.
Every cell.
Everything.
Then I'll be killed.
So what?
What'd you work out
with that man?
That man?
That son of a bitch
saw the light.
He saw through Dwight Manfredi.
straight on back
to his goat-fucking ancestors
in Sicily.
Now it's our time
to even the score.
Dwight Manfredi
was gonna bomb our house.
our home.
where you and your brother
were raised...
and your mama passed.
He was gonna kill us both.
And then the Lord
redirected his hand.
How?
We'll kill several birds
with one righteous stone.
I'm gonna succeed
where you failed.
Some roaches won't be checking
out of their hotel tonight.
Hey. look here.
So. every envelope.
we got to kick up. okay?
Boss got to get his cut. It's
just the cost of doing business.
I got it.
You sound like Goodie.
I'm just saying. you know?
Hey. but look.
business is booming over here.
I-I give you that.
I give it to you.
I give it to you. I see you.
- I see you.
- Tell me about it.
- we're almost out.
- Oh. yeah?
All right. I'm-a. I'm-a go get
some more over here.
and. you know.
we gonna do our thing.
Yo.
A'ight. a'ight. a'ight.
What are you doing here. Cole?
- If Tyson sees you...
- I know.
I know. It's just...
my father said something.
What?
He said something about hurting
people close to Manfredi.
And you're close to him. so...
Did he say any more?
Something about a hotel...
and hurting a lot of people.
Stay here.
I will be right back.
Yeah. I can tell you crazy.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
What the fuck?
Goddamn. Ow. ow!
Cole showed up.
You said what? That-that
motherfucker here right now?
Wait. listen. he said Dunmire's
planning something tonight.
Fuck that guy.
I don't give a fuck.
He said something about a hotel
and hurting a lot of people.
Hotel?
Oh. shit.
Look at me.
Anything else
you want to remember?
Think hard.
No. No.
- You got all that?
- Oh. I got it all on tape.
- We done here?
- Almost.
Remember this?
Now I'm done.
Get him out of here.
With pleasure.
Fuck. Tyson. yeah. What's up?
What?
Fuck.
Musso!
Where the hell are you?
- Where's the target?
- The target?
It doesn't matter where
the fucking target is.
This maniac. this fucking Deacon
put a fucking bomb
at the Delmore Grand Hotel.
And how the fuck
do you know that?
How do I know?
I got him right in front of me.
You fucking speak up now.
Pull him up.
Tell him. Did you put a bomb
at the Grand Hotel?
Yeah.
- Yes? Louder!
- Yes.
And what time?
What time?!
Ten.
Speak up.
- Ten.
- You fucking hear that?
Now get over there!
I'm on my way.
No! No!
Go!
Come on. Margaret. come on.
Fuck.
Faith-based initiatives.
Traditional American values.
Those are the pillars
of my platform.
And I'm not just talking
about tradition.
I'm talking about protecting
the community.
Giving the people a voice
to stand up to the noise.
All good talking points.
which I've heard
from every candidate
in every election cycle.
What Mr. Thresher means is.
he's not just pledging support.
He's pledging
membership. tithes.
Absolutely.
Ten percent from a billionaire.
You could build
a hundred new sanctuaries.
a new church in every city.
Not just influencing policy
but leading it.
Dr. Johnson.
Faith is not a campaign promise.
It's a movement.
Conviction and commitment
are in short supply
- these days.
- Mm.
You have my support.
Thank you very much.
Fuck!
Yes. it's real. There's a
fucking bomb at the fundraiser.
Meet us there.
Tyson will be there in 20.
Got to evacuate now!
Hold on.
Need to evac now!
Everyone. there's a bomb threat!
Everybody out!
Right now. right now!
Let's go. let's go!
Bomb threat!
Everybody out!
Now! Now! Now! Now!
Move! Bomb!
- Bomb threat!
- Come on. move!
Come on!
Goddamn. hurry the fuck up.
Everyone move quickly
and calmly to the exit!
That's right.
everybody out! Come on!
Margaret! Margaret.
Margaret!
Come with me. come with me.
Let's go. right here.
Everybody. now. come on.
Come on. out this way.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go! Margaret!
Margaret.
- You okay?
- Yes.
We got to go. we got to go.
Two minutes.
Two fucking minutes.
Come on. Right this way.
Move your ass! Move!
Get out. get out. come on.
Is there anybody left?
Let's go.
Is there anybody left?!
Are you okay? Are you all right?
Yeah. yeah. I'm... I'm good.
Thank God.
Cole?
Yeah.
I can always sense
when you're nearby.
I heard there was a...
a ruckus at that
wannabe governor's party.
Some people shouldn't be
where they shouldn't be.
I'm glad it worked out for you.
Always does.
Who is that?
We'll talk later.
Help me get up.
Help me get up. I'm okay.
Goddamn.
Hold on. Hold on.
I'm just gonna chat with him.
then I'll be back.
Well. what the fuck?
So what do you want to do?
Bury you. You broke our deal.
That's only in your mind.
No. no. no.
It doesn't work like that.
You fucked everything up.
Where is he?
Out of sight. out of mind.
What matters is still in here.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. but you got
to share that with me.
Maybe tomorrow.
It's been a long night.
I'm not going anywhere.
No. you're not.
Tomorrow.